Guide to the Stephen Henry Schneider Papers SC1053
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Publications, Series 5
  - Articles
    - Life in the Universe (A Special Issue of Scientific American) "The Evolution of the Earth" (SHS & Claude J, Allegre), 1994 (Box 199, Folder 31)
    - World Monitor - "Cooling It: The Global Warming Debate" (SHS), 1990 July (Box 199, Folder 32)
    - Global Climate Change, An East Room Roundtable, 1997 July (Box 199, Folder 33)
    - Food-Climate Interactions: Issues & Policy Implications (SHS and Wilfred Bach), 1980 July (Box 199, Folder 34)
    - Climatic Barriers to Long-Term Energy Growth - SHS and Roger D. Dennett in Ambio, 1975 (Box 199, Folder 35)
    - Ecology & Climate: Research Strategies & Implications (SHS & TLR), 1995 April (Box 199, Folder 36)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists "Employ Market Incentives" (SHS), 2007 Jan/Feb (Box 199, Folder 37)
    - Biodiversity and Conservation - "Ecological Implications of Climate Change will include surprises" (SHS), 1996 (Box 199, Folder 38)
    - Predicting the Unpredictable (Nasty Surprises) [drafts, comments], 1976-1977 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Food/Climate monograph [draft summary, outline, comments] - SHS with Bach, 1980 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Food Climate Interactions: Issues and Policy Implications & correspondence (copy 1), 1980 July (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Food Climate Interactions: Issues and Policy Implications & correspondence (copy 2), 1980 July (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Airways, 1988 June (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - To Not Decide is to Decide (commission for the future), 1988 September (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - The Greenhouse Effect: Science and Policy pg. 771 (AAAS) Science Vol. 243, 1989 February (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Natural Resources and Environment (SHS interview) - 2 copies, 1989 Summer (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Impact Assessment, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Encyclopedia Article - Climate and Weather, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Local Warming - NCAR, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Buzzworm - SHS, 1990 November (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Necrology for J. Murray Mitchell (obituary), 1990 November (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - W. O. Roberts Book - SHS, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - The Global Warming Debate: Science or Politics? - Environmental Science and Technology, 1990 April (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Good Housekeeping "Dealing with the Greenhouse Effect", 1991 April (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - World Monitor "Our Waste-Free House", 1991 June (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - "Global Warming" in Flower and Garden Magazine (SHS vs. Dixy Lee Ray), 1991 Aug/Sept (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - A Critical Review in Conservation Biology (SHS and TLR) 1/2, 1991 Sept (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - A Critical Review - Conservation Biology Root - SHS 2/2, 1991 Sept (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - Melampus Journal, 1991 Sept (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - Michigan Newsletter #1, 1991 September (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - Fire or Ice? Once Again - Discover Magazine, 1991 December (Box 200, Folder 23)
    - Are we ready for International Action? - TLCP Journal, 1991 December (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - Gaia - World Book, 1992 September (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - Comment on Nordhaus Dice Model - Science, 1992 December (Box 200, Folder 26)
    - From Ruth Gill (correspondence), 1994 (Box 200, Folder 27)
    - Is a Citizen-Scientist an Oxymoron?, 1997 Feburary 18, 1993 Feb 12, also 1996 (Box 200, Folder 28)
    - Broad Consensus on "Scientific Cleansing" - Brownlash Monitor, 1997 March (Box 200, Folder 29)
    - Aspen - AGCI Reprints - Characterizing and Communicating Scientific Uncertainty [draft], 1997 (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - SHS Handwritten notes for a talk in Chicago - systems thinking in education, multiple intelligences, 1998 (Box 200, Folder 31)
    - interview, 1999 (Box 200, Folder 32)
    - SHS Handwritten Notes, 1999-2000 (Box 200, Folder 33)
    - Patient from Hello Handwritten Notes, 2002 (Box 200, Folder 34)
    - SHS Handwritten list of impediments and solutions, undated (Box 200, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, circa 1979 (Box 200, Folder 36)
    - Ice Ages and Orbital Cariations by Schneider & Thompson, 1978 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Seasonal Simulation as a Test for Uncertainties by Warren & Schneider, 1979 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - A Seasonal Zonal Energy Balance Climate Model by Schneider & Thompson, 1979 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Atmospheric CO2 and Climate by Schneider & Thompson, 1981 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Coupled Climate Systems: memos & draft plans by SHS, circa 1987 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Goddess of the Earth? Debate over GAIA by SHS - draft & correspondence, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Paleoclimatic and Paleoecological Analyses by Schneider, 1993 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Cooling It: article for Microsoft Encarta Encyclopedia, 1998 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - National Biological Survey Status & Trends Report: drafts and correspondence (1/4), 1995 March (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - National Biological Survey Status & Trends Report: drafts and correspondence (2/4), 1995 March (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - National Biological Survey Status & Trends Report: drafts and correspondence (3/4), 1995 March (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - National Biological Survey Status & Trends Report: drafts and correspondence (4/4), 1995 March (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Earth Systems Textbook - Chapter 1 by SHS, 1997 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Global Carbon Dioxide Emissions Scenarios by Yang & Schneider (1/7) (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - Global Carbon Dioxide Emissions Scenarios by Yang & Schneider (2/7) (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Global Carbon Dioxide Emissions Scenarios by Yang & Schneider (3/7) (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - Global Carbon Dioxide Emissions Scenarios by Yang & Schneider (4/7) (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - Global Carbon Dioxide Emissions Scenarios by Yang & Schneider (5/7) (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - Global Carbon Dioxide Emissions Scenarios by Yang & Schneider (6/7) (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - Global Carbon Dioxide Emissions Scenarios by Yang & Schneider (7/7) (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Ecology & Climate: Research strategies and implications by Root & Schneider, 1995 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - Human effect on global climate? Letters to Science, 1996 (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - Scientist Debate Gaia: The Next Century - MIT press by Schneider et. al, 2004 (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - Gaia Press File (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Publications by SHS (Box 214, Folder 25)
    - Open Letter to the President and Members of Congress on Climate, 2009 (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - Articles and correspondence with Eric Selmon, 1997 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - "Energy article" with Eric Selmon [drafts], 1995-1997 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - "Energy article" with Eric Selmon [drafts and submissions], 1995-1997 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - "Energy article" with Eric Selmon [drafts and submissions], 1995-1997 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Selmon & Schneider Energy / Environment Curric Enhancement, 1995-1997 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - "Bright Idea" / "Energy" with Eric Selmon [drafts], 1995-1996 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Imaginable Surprise "Climate Change Policy", 1998-1999 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - "Quantifying Uncertainties for Damage from Climatic Change" - Tim Roughgarden with SHS, 1997-1999 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Imaginable Surprise, 1997 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Imaginable Surprise - SHS and B.L. Turner, 1996 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Imaginable Surprise - SHS and B.L. Turner, 1997 (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Imaginable Surprise - SHS and B.L. Turner, 1997 (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - "Brownlash Monitor article" [SHS and Paul N. Edwards], 1997 (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - Sierra [ad, pg. 16], 2008 Jan/Feb (Box 215, Folder 14)
    - Discover [pg. 72], 2005 April (Box 215, Folder 15)
    - The Climate for Greenhouse Policy (1/3) (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - The Climate for Greenhouse Policy (2/3) (Box 215, Folder 17)
    - The Climate for Greenhouse Policy (3/3) (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - No Therapy for the Earth: chapter, drafts, correspondence, etc. (1/2) (Box 215, Folder 19)
    - No Therapy for the Earth: chapter, drafts, correspondence, etc. (2/2) (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - Climatic Barriers to Long-Term Energy Growth - Ambio, 1975 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Comparative Risk Assesment of Energy Systems, 1979 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - letter to the editor of the Denver Post, 1989 Feb 21 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - "Forecasting with a Hierarchy of Models: Examples from Climate Modeling" - National Academy of Sciences 1st Annual Symposium on Frontiers of Science, 1989 March (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Human Biology: Health and Homeostasis - "The Global Warming Debate Heats Up but the Problem Remains the Same", 1990 March (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - Journal of the Japan Society of Civil Engineers - Global Warming - Science and Policy, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - World Monitor - "Cooling It", 1990 (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - Greenpeace / Dr. Jeremy Leggett, Dr. Kailee "Shadow IPCC" (1/2), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - Greenpeace / Dr. Jeremy Leggett, Dr. Kailee "Shadow IPCC" (2/2), 1990 (Box 227, Folder 9)
    - Prediction of Future Climate Change - New Scientist, 1990 June 11 (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - The Global Warming Debate: Science or Politics? - Parliamentary Forum on Global Climate Change - Ottawa, Canada, 1990 April 23 (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - Archives and Records [NCAR], 1991 December 4 (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - The Global Warming Debate: Science or Politics? - Environmental Science and Technology, 1990-1991 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - Technology Review letter, 1992 May/June (Box 227, Folder 14)
    - National Geographic Resources / expl. - "Degrees of Certainty", 1992-1993 (Box 227, Folder 15)
    - Detecting Climatic Change Signals: Are there any Fingerprints? - Science (1/2), 1993 November (Box 227, Folder 16)
    - Detecting Climatic Change Signals: Are there any Fingerprints? - Science [includes 35mm slides] (2/2), 1993 November (Box 227, Folder 17)
    - "old" Fingerprints (1/2), 1993 (Box 227, Folder 18)
    - "old" Fingerprints (2/2), 1993 (Box 227, Folder 19)
    - The Global Warming Debate: Are there public health implications?, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 20)
    - Global Warming commisioned piece for Newsweek, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 21)
    - The Global Warming Debate: Are there public policy implications? - UCLA symposium [1993] "Human Population and the Environmental Crisis" [includes diskette], 1994 August (Box 227, Folder 22)
    - Evolutionary Organizational Models for Interdisciplinary Research and Teaching of Global Environmental Change, 1994 September (Box 227, Folder 23)
    - Aspen Global Abstract "Surprise and Global Environmental Change" - Chang and Billie, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 24)
    - Bets and "Ecofantasies", 1995 (Box 227, Folder 25)
    - Nature - Achieving Low-Cost Emissions Targets (1/2), 1997 March (Box 227, Folder 26)
    - Nature - Achieving Low-Cost Emissions Targets (2/2), 1997 March (Box 227, Folder 27)
    - Defining and teaching encironmental literacy, 1997 (Box 227, Folder 28)
    - Sustainable Development and Global Change: Poles of Science, Uncertainty and Citizen, 1997 (Box 227, Folder 29)
    - Energy / Environment Curriculum Enhancement: "Real World" Projects Confronting Obstacles to Energy Efficiency Implementation in Local Institutions [unpublished], 1997 (Box 227, Folder 30)
    - Global Climate Change in the Human Perspective, 2000 Jan (Box 227, Folder 31)
    - Comment on "Thermal Pollution Causes Global Warming" - Global and Planetary Change, 2005 (Box 227, Folder 32)
    - Human-modified temperatures induce species changes: Joint attribution, 2005 May 24 (Box 227, Folder 33)
    - "Climate Change, Elevational Range Shifts, and Bird Extinctions" - Conservation Biology, 2007 (Box 227, Folder 34)
    - Reducing Greenhouse Gas Emissions in the US: How Far and How Fast [unpublished], 2007 (Box 227, Folder 35)
    - "Dangerous" Climate Change: Key Vulnerabilities, 2007 (Box 227, Folder 36)
    - The Worst-Case Scenario - Nature, 2009 April (Box 227, Folder 37)
    - Volcanic Dust, Sunspots and Long-Term Climate Trends: Theories in Search of Verification, 1975 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - On the Carbon-Dioxide - Climate Confusion (1/2), 1975 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - On the Carbon-Dioxide - Climate Confusion (2/2), 1975 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Human Nature, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Seasonal Simulation as a Test for Uncertainties in the Parameterization of a Budyko Sellers Zonal Climate Model (SHS and Stephen G. Warren), 1979 Feb 15 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Carbon Dioxide Warming and Coastline Flooding: An Example of a Physical, Economic and Social Climatic Impact Assessment (SHS and Robert S. Chen), 1979 August (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Some Realistic Modifications of Simple Climate Models, 1979 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Carbon-Dioxide Warming and Coastline Flooding (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Carbon-Dioxide Warming and Coastline Flooding (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - Food-Climate Interactions: Issues and Policy Statements, 1980 (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - Atmospheric CO2 and Climate: Importance of the Transient Response, 1981 April 20 (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - Carbon Dioxide Warming and Coastal Flooding, 1981 July (Box 229, Folder 12)
    - CO2 aned Climate: Has a Signal Been Observed Yet? (SHS and Starley Thompson), 1982 Feb 3 (Box 229, Folder 13)
    - Social Science Research and Climate Change (SHS, Robert Chen, Elise Boulding), 1983 (Box 229, Folder 14)
    - Changes in direction / focus @ NCAR - "interdisciplinary" "system", 1983-1986 (Box 229, Folder 15)
    - Coupled Climate Systems: A New Initiative in Atmospheric Science at NCAR, 1986 June (Box 229, Folder 16)
    - Coupled Climate System Memos, 1986 (Box 229, Folder 17)
    - Dan Druckman Proposal (National Research Council) - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change, 1989-1991 (Box 229, Folder 18)
    - "Dan Druckman report" - HDGC draft (1/3), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 19)
    - "Dan Druckman report" (2/3), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 20)
    - "Dan Druckman report" (3/3), 1990 (Box 229, Folder 21)
    - The World Book Encyclopedia "Gaia" Entry, 1995 Feb 17 (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - Interchapter: the Greenhouse Effect" (interview transcript), 1994 Sept 19 (Box 246, Folder 12)
    - Energy Implications of CO2 Stabilization (drafts w/ comments), 1997 Nov 6 (Box 246, Folder 13)
    - NBS Status and Trends (drafts), 1995 Feb (Box 246, Folder 14)
  - Websites
    - SHS Website, 2006-2007 (Box 168, Folder 36)
    - Website: text & correspondence (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Website: content (draft material) (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Website: comments, circa 2003 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Website: permissions requests (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Website: miscellaneous & links, circa 2003 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Website: miscellaneous (Box 192, Item 6-10)
    - for Climate Change.net website, Sept. 2005 (Box 201, Folder 48)
      - World wide web views on global warming, 2009 (Box 201, Folder 49)
- Conferences, Meetings, and Professional Travel, Series 6
  - Phytopathological Society/World Food Population Confrontation, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - American Geophysical Union –"Public Policy Issues in Climatic Change" (Schneider), 1976 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Travel vouchers, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Abrupt Climatic Change, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - International Association of Meteorology and Atmospheric Physics (IAMP), 1985 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Travel vouchers, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR), 1985 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS); U.S. water resources panel, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - American Geophysical Union, 1986 (Box 83, Item 9-10)
  - Annenberg School: Global Disasters and Information Flows, 1986 (Box 83, Item 11-13)
  - COHMAP workshop, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation (IGCC) seminar, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - JASON meeting, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - MacArthur Foundation in International Security, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Man and Beast Revisited, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - International Decade of Hazard Reduction, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Natural Hazards workshop, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Rocky Mountain Division - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1986 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Travel vouchers, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - University of Rhode Island, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Wellesley College, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Workshop on Atmospheric Change, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), meeting 1987 (Box 83, Item 25-26)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), retreat, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Climate Global Dynamics (CGD), 1987 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Colby College, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Denver World Affairs Council, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Department of Energy (DOE) meeting on global environmental research, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) workshop, 1987 (Box 83, Item 32-33)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Global Climate Change workshop, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Federation of American Scientists (FAS), 1987 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Global Science Seminar (Scripps), 1987 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Global Conflict and Cooperation (IGCC), Seminar on Global Security, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Los Alamos, Future Climatic Change, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) seminar, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Climate Dynamics, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - North American Conference on Preparing for Climate Change, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - NATO workshop, Paleoclimatology and Paleometeorology, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Polar Research Committee on Glaciology, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Risk Analysis and Management of Natural and Man-Made Hazards, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - St. Olaf College, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Santa Fe Institute, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Social Science Research Council, AIDS conference, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Sister City Project, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Symposium on Climate and People, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Travel vouchers, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Forest Service workshop, 1987 (Box 84, Item 18-19)
  - University of Chicago, seminar, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - World Wildlife Fund, Greenhouse symposium, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Agribusiness conference, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Workshop in Earth System Science, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), meeting, 1988 (Box 84, Item 24-25)
  - Arizona Honors Academy seminar, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Changing Atmosphere conference, 1988 (Box 84, Item 27-30)
  - Climate and Geo-Sciences conference, 1988 (Box 85, Item 1-4)
  - Climate Change and Economic Growth, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Climate Variability and Ecosystem Response, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Controlling and Adapting to Greenhouse Warming, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Council for the Advancement of Science Writing (CASW), New Horizons program, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - COSEPUP planning meeting on climate change, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Earth System Science workshop, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Federal Agency Response to Global Climate Change, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Federation of American Scientists (FAS) meeting, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Global Catastrophes in Earth History, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Greenhouse 88 - Planning for Climate Change, 1988 (Box 85, Item 14-15)
  - International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (IIASA) meeting, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - National Academy of Engineering (NAE), Technology and Environment workshop, 1988 (Box 85, Item 17-18)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) meeting, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) white papers, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Academy of Sciences, USSR (ASUSSR), Global Ecology meeting, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Office for Interdisciplinary Earth Studies (OIES), Global Climate Change Institute, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Office for Interdisciplinary Earth Studies (OIES), Congressional and Scientific Forum on Global Earth Studies, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Rotary Club, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Rutgers University, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Second North American Conference on Preparing for Climate Change, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Travel vouchers, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - University of Virginia, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Wildfire Severity Workshop, 1988 (Box 85, Item 29-31)
  - Wirth Seminar on Global warming, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - World Resources Institute (WRI) seminar, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), Consequences of the Greenhouse Effect for Biological Diversity, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Declined conference invitations, 1988-1989 (Box 86, Item 1-3)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) symposium, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - American Bar Association (ABA) interview, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - American Chemical Society (ACS) plenary, Atmospheric Modeling, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - American Solar Energy Society, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Aspen Institute, executive seminar, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Aspen Institute, Global Commons, 1989 (Box 86, Item 9-10)
  - Auburn University, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Cairo Climate Conference, 1989 (Box 86, Item 12-13)
  - Casey Junior High School, Eco-day, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Choices for a Healthy Environment (Windstar Foundation), 1989 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Climate Change and Water Resources in the Tennessee Valley and Inland Southeast, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Colorado Ski Country meeting, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Endangered Environment, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Environmental Defense Fund (EDF) lecture, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) meeting, 1989 (Box 86, Item 20-21)
  - Explorers Club, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Exxon Research, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Forum on Global Climate Change and our Common Future, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Gas Research Conference (Japan), 1989 (Box 86, Item 25-26)
  - Global Change: Colorado's Risks and Opportunities, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Global Climate workshop, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - The Global Environment: Are we Overreacting?, 1989 (Box 86, Item 29-30)
  - Greenhouse Effect, Commonwealth Lecture, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Greenhouse Effect lecture, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Human Demography and Natural Resources, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Implications of Climate Change for Africa, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Institute for Environmental Studies (IES), University of Wisconsin, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - International Law and Global Change, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Issues Confronting the Global Future, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - KIRO News, Distinguished Meteorologist Program, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Michigan Tech. (Greenhouse Effect lecture), 1989 (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS) symposium, Frontiers of Science, 1989 (Box 87, Item 1-2)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research (NCAR), advisory meeting, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Office for Interdisciplinary Earth Studies (OIES), Global Change Institute, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility – Our Common Future, Healing the Planet, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Planet in Peril conference, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 7)